Finding Aid for the A&M Records Records PASC-M.0269
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sound recordings, 1910-1999; Series 12.
  - Commercial popular music: 33 1/3 rpm LP sound recordings, Subseries 6.
    - The Trouble With Normal, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 43, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: GM 3283
      The Trouble With Normal -- Candy Man's Gone -- Hoop Dancer -- Waiting For The Moon -- Tropic Moon -- Going Up Against Chaos -- Put Our Hearts Together -- Civilization And Its Discontents -- Planet Of The Clowns.
    - Wings (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: SP 3503
    - Jessi Colter, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: ST-11363
    - Old Fool Back On Earth, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: C2X 38211
    - The Man And His Music, 1986; 2 12" sound discs (Box 46, Folder 33)
      Publisher no.: CPL2-7127
      Touch the Hem Of His Garment -- That's Heaven To Me -- I'll Come running Back To You -- You Send Me -- Win Your Love For Me -- Just For You -- Chain Gang -- When A Boy Falls In Love -- Only Sixteen -- Wonderful World -- Cupid -- Nothing Can Change This Love -- Rome Wasn't Built In A Day -- Love Will Find A Way -- Everybody Loves To Cha Cha Cha -- Another Saturday Night -- Meet Me At Mary's Place -- Having A Party -- Good Times -- Twistin' The Night Away -- Shake -- Somebody Have Mercy -- Sad Mood -- Ain't That Good News -- Bring It On Home To Me -- Soothe Me -- That's Where It's At -- A Change Is Gonna Come.
    - The Rhythmatist, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: SP 5084
      Koteja (Oh Bolilla) -- Brazzaville -- Liberte -- Coco -- Kemba -- Samburu Sunset -- Gong Rock -- Franco -- Serengeti Long Walk -- African Dream.
    - The Song Of Singing (Box 41, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: BST 84353
    - The Cotton Club, Original motion picture soundtrack, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 177, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: GHS 24062 E
      The Mooche -- Cotton Club Stomp #2 -- Drop Me Off In Harlem -- Creole Love Call -- Ring Dem Bells -- East St. Louis Toodle-O -- Truckin' -- Ill Wind -- Cotton Club Stomp #1 -- Mood Indigo -- Minnie the Moocher -- Copper Colored Gal -- Dixie Kidnaps Vera -- The Depression Hits/Best Beats Sandman -- Daybreak Express Medley.
    - Wild Child, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 32)
      Publisher no.: SP 6 5081
      Is Anybody Home? -- Little Toy -- Love In the Shadows -- Just For You -- Hey There Rocky -- Say It, Say It -- Wild Child -- Don't Let Them Take the Child Away -- Waiting -- Sunset People.
    - Aldo Romano (Box 45, Folder 36)
      Publisher no.: 3800501
      Also performed by: Paolo Fresu, and Furio Di Castri.
    - The Lost Weekend, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: SP 6 5075
      The Word Is Out -- Song for the Dreamers -- Miracle Mile -- Baby, We All Gotta Go Down -- The King Of Losers -- Send Me A Postcard -- Down To the Bone -- Knockin' On Heaven's Door.
    - Carmel By the Sea, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: MS-100
      When It's Gonna Hit -- Carmello -- Solo Flight -- You and I -- Cleared for Take-Off -- Rising Starr -- King Pong -- Lush Life.
    - The Man With The Horn, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: FC 36790
    - Water Babies, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 29)
      Publisher no.: PC 34396
    - Tutu (Box 48, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: 9-237554
    - Boomtown, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 34)
      Publisher no.: SP 6-5134
      Welcome To the Boomtown -- Swallowed By the Cracks -- Ain't So Easy -- Being Alone Together -- A Rock For the Forgotten -- River's Gonna Rise -- Swimming In the Ocean -- All Alone In the Big City -- Heroes.
    - The Optimist (Box 44, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: L38225
    - Back To the World (Box 171, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: SP 5109
      This Is the Time -- Warning Shot -- Call Me -- Unanswered Prayers -- Black Wall -- Southbound Ryan -- I'll Get Lucky -- Person To Person.
    - Into the Light, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: AMA 5121
    - Best Moves, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      Publisher no.: AMLH 68532
    - Into The Light, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: SP 5121
    - Man On The Line, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: 1113 3980
    - Say No Go (Box 41, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: BLR 10 T
    - Sandy, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: SP 4371
    - C'mon And Get My Love, 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 43, Folder 29)
      Publisher no.: 886 799-1
      On jacket, "Introducing Cathy Dennis." 12" single.
    - Prelude, 1972 (Box 169, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: CTI 6021
      Also Sprach Zarathustra (2001) -- Spirit of Summer -- Carly & Carole -- Baubles, Bangles and Beads -- Prelude to Afternoon of a Faun -- September 13.
    - Wake 'Em Up In Tokyo, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 30)
    - Hot August Night, 1972 (Box 169, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: MCA 2-8000
      Prolgue -- Crunchy Granola -- Done Too Soon -- Solitary Man -- Cherry Cherry -- Sweet Caroline -- Porcupine Pie -- You're So Sweet -- Red Red Wine -- Soggy Pretzels -- And the Grass Won't Pay No Mind -- Shilo -- Girl You'll Be A Woman Soon -- Play Me -- Canta Libre -- Morningside -- Song Sung Blue -- Cracklin' Rosie -- Holly Holly -- I Am .. I Said -- Soolaimon/Brother's Love -- (Encore).
    - Love Over Gold, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: 23728-1
    - Money For Nothing (Box 48, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: 9-25794-1
    - Love Is All, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: NSPL 18504
    - Djavan, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: FC 39973
    - Bird Of Paradise, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: FC 44276
    - Romantic Music (Box 44, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: C10-23083 006
    - Timofei Dokshitser With Ensembles (Box 44, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: C10 28215 004
    - Lady In Blue, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: NSPL 18461
    - The Dorsey/Sinatra Radio Years, 1940-42 And The Historic Stordahl Session, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: AFL-4741
      Also performed by Frank Sinatra.
    - Blue, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: SP 5133
    - Blue, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 16)
      Woman Of the World -- I Know A Place -- The Captain Of Her Heart -- Your Prayer Takes Me Off -- Rangoon Moon -- Urban Nomads -- Love Is A Plane -- Tomorrow.
    - All 'N All (Box 170, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: 34905
      Serpentine Fire -- Fantasy -- In the Marketplace -- Jupiter -- Love's Holiday -- Brazillian Rhyme -- I'll Write A Song For You -- Magic Mind -- Runnin' -- Brazillian Rhyme -- Be Ever Wonderful.
    - Vol. 1, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: FC 35647
      Got to Get You Into My Life -- Singasong -- Shing Star -- Getaway -- Can't Hide Love -- Fantasy -- That;'s the Way Of the World -- Reasons -- September -- Love Music.
      On jacket: see label for sequence.
    - I Am, 1979 (Box 170, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: 35730
      In the Stone -- Can't Let Go -- After the Love Is Gone -- Let Your Feelings Show -- Boogie Wonderland -- Star -- Wait -- Rock That! -- You and I.
    - East Memphis Music, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      Box set, 2 copies
    - Morning (opus one), 255667.1 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      two copies (one just the sleeve)
    - Almost Blue, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: FC 37562
    - What Is Beat?, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 43, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: SP70040
      Mirror In The Bathroom -- Twist & Crawl -- Tears Of A Clown -- Can't Get Used To Losing You -- Doors Of Your Heart -- What's Your Best Thing -- Hit It -- Save It For Later -- Best Friends -- I Confess -- Too Nice To Talk To -- Get A Job -- Stand Down Margaret.
    - Melissa Etheridge, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 43, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: 7 90875-1
      Similar Features -- Chrome Plated Heart -- Like The Way I Do -- Precious Pain -- Don't You Need -- The Late September Dogs -- Occasionally -- Watching You -- Bring Me Some Water -- I Want You.
    - Mystic Line, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: NSPL 18473
    - Sounds Of Blackness, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 28)
      Also performed by: Frankie Knuckles, Jimmy Jam, and Terry Lewis.
    - Einzelhaft, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: AMLH 68550
    - 3, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: SP 5105
      Rock Me Amadeus -- America -- Tango the Night -- Munich Girls (Looking For Love) -- Jeanny -- Vienna Calling -- Manner Des Westens - Any Kind Of Land -- Nothin' Sweeter Than Arabia -- Macho Macho -- It's All Over Now, Baby Blue.
    - Fats Navarro, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: 0798
    - Live At The Algonquin, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Pure Gershwin, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - [Selections], 1986 April 14; Side B. Mastercut. (Box 62, Folder 7)
      Sunday -- Taxi -- 2nd Emotion -- Bang On Boxes -- Zazu.
    - Enseame, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: DIL-80356
    - A Perfect Match, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 33)
      Publisher no.: D2312110
      Also performed by Count Basie.
    - Digital III at Montreux, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 35)
      Publisher no.: D2308223
      Also performed by: Joe Pass, and Count Basie.
    - Phoenix, 1979 (Box 169, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: FE 35634
      Tullamore Dew -- Phoenix -- Gypsy Wind -- The Last To Know -- Face The Fire -- Wishing On the Moon -- Heart Hotels -- Longer -- Beggar's Game -- Along the Road.
    - Songs For The tempted (Box 42, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: 465348-1
    - Better Than Swimming (Box 45, Folder 40)
      Publisher no.: NECK 001 EP
    - Sour Cream & Other Delights, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 33)
      Publisher no.: LSP-3663
    - Aux Armes et Caetera (Box 45, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: PG 210
    - Tran-Siberian Express (Box 44, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: C60 27669 007
    - Song Of Seashore And Other Melodies Of Japan, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: ARL1-3534
    - Kiss Of Life, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: CAM-395
    - That Warm Feeling (Box 47, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: MG V-2088
      Also performed by: Roy Eldridge.
    - All The Rage, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 43, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: SP 70046
      Hot You're Cool -- Tenderness -- Anxious -- Never You Done That -- Burning Bright -- As A Matter Of Fact -- Are You Leading Me On -- Day To Day -- Where's The Line -- General Public -- Yes We're In A Group.
    - Apasionado (Box 32, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: 75021 5297 1
    - For Musicians Only (Box 47, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: MGV-8198
      Also performed by Dizzy Gillespie and Sonny Stitt.
    - Focus, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: Ve-1-2528
    - Apasionado, 1990; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Apasionado -- Coba -- Waltz for Stan -- Espanola -- Madrugado -- Amorous Cat -- Midnight Ride -- Lonely Lady.
    - Concert Of The Century (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Life, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: FC 39423
    - Night Full Of Tension (Box 44, Folder 30)
      Publisher no.: STUMM16
    - Sleepless Nights, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: SP 5037
      Up -- Electric Between Us -- Diary Of A Fool -- That Kinda Girl -- I Can Take It -- The Girl Upstairs -- Sleepless Nights -- The Age Of Steam -- In the Jungle.
    - Sleepless Nights, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Every Heartbeat (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: 75021 2361 1
    - Baby Baby, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: 75021 7516 1
    - Serie Laboratorio, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Straight Ahead, 1984 (Box 171, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: SP 5058
      Where Do You Hide Your Heart -- Jehovah -- Angels -- Straight Ahead -- Thy Word -- It's Not A Song -- Open Arms -- Doubly Good To You -- Tomorrow -- The Now And the Not Yet.
    - He Is The Light, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: SP 5102
    - Al Green Greatest Hits (Box 44, Folder 23)
      Publisher no.: 5283ML
    - Movin' On, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: NSPL 18413
    - Hearts And Numbers, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: HP 106
    - Brasil 66 Medley, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: C12Y3163
    - Lo Mejor de Lani, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: C28Y3157
    - Lo Mejor de Lani, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      no LP; sleeve only
    - Hello It's Me, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: SP 4508
    - Sweet Bird (Box 36, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: SP 4617
    - Double Or Nothing, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: SP-4760
    - Albany Park, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: SP-4898
    - Collectibles, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: SP-4988
      5 copies.
    - A Brazileira, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: SP-020105
    - Lani Hall, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: SP-30002
    - Es Facil Amar, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: SP 37012
    - Lani Hall, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: SP-37008
    - Lo Mejor de Lani, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: SP-37018
    - Lani Hall, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: SP 37601
    - [Selections], 1974 December 6; 1 12" sound disc (Box 62, Folder 2)
      Hello, It's Me -- Peace in the Valley -- Time Will Tell -- Banquet -- Wheelers & Dealers -- Happy Woman -- Exclusively For Me -- Save the Sunlight -- Sweet Jams & Jellies -- Correida de Jangada.
      Mastercut.
    - Blush, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Where's Your Angel -- In the Dark -- Come What May -- Love Me Again -- No Strings -- Ain't Got Nothin' for Me -- Wish I Would've Stayed -- I Don't Want You to Go -- Only You.
    - Hamp In Paris (Box 42, Folder 37)
      Publisher no.: MG 36032
    - Hank De Mano Quartet In Concert, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Angels Will Be Singing (Box 41, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: BRS-4045/7014045024
      Also performed by The Music & Arts Seminar Mass Choir.
    - Outside, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: 75021 7393 1
    - Watching My Life Go By, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 39)
      Publisher no.: OA-0303
    - Live On The Double Planet (Box 48, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: WH-1066
    - Songs I Sing, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: NSPL 18459
    - Bring The Family, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: SP 5158
    - Hai Hai, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: SP 5112
    - [Selections] (Box 62, Folder 3)
      Am I Blue -- Bluesette -- Honeysuckle -- People -- I Believe In You -- Danny Boy.
    - Nervous Night, 1985 (Box 170, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: BFC 39912
      And We Danced -- Day By Day -- All You Zombies -- Don't Take My Car Out Tonight -- Hanging On A Heartbeat -- Where Do the Children Go -- South Ferry Road -- She Comes In Colors -- Blood From A Stone.
    - Whitney Houston, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: AL 8-8212
    - The Zawinul Syndicate, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: FC 40969
    - Supertramp (Box 33, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: SP 4311
    - It's Your Night, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: 23970-1
    - The Posse (Shoot 'Em Up) (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: 31458 0237 1
    - The Steadfast Tin Soldier (Box 48, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: WH-0702
    - The 1814 Megamix (full version) -- Black Cat (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: AMYDJ 587
    - Will Power, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: SP 3908
    - Body and Soul, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: SP-5000
    - You Can't Get What You Want (till you know what you want), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: SP 12098
    - Miss You Much [remixes], 1989 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: SP-17925
    - Thriller, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: QE 38112
    - Night And Day (Box 44, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: MFSL 1-080
    - Control, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: SP 5106
      Control -- Nasty -- What Have You Done For Me Lately -- You Can Be Mine -- The Pleasure Principle -- When I Think Of You -- He Doesn't Know I'm Alive -- Let's Wait A While -- Funny How Time Flies (When You're Having Fun).
    - Shockadelica (Box 171, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: SP 5122
      Change Your Mind -- Crazay -- Baby Let's Kiss -- A Better Way -- Do Yourself A Favor -- She (I Can't Resist) -- Addiction -- Tonite -- Burn You Up -- Black In America.
    - Big World (Box 171, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: SP 6021
      Wild West -- Right and Wrong -- (It's A) Big World -- Precious Time -- Tonight and Forever -- Shanghai Sky -- Fifty Dollar Love Affair -- We Can't Live Together -- Forty Years -- Survival -- Soul Kiss -- The Jet Set -- Tango Atlantico -- Home Town -- Man In the Street.
    - Miss You Much, 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 12315
    - When I Think of You, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 12193
    - Find The Vagabonds Now, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: NSPL 18495
    - WWII, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 46, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: AHL1-4455
      Mr. Shuck and Jive -- Roman Candles -- (Sittin' on) The Dock of the Bay -- The Year That Clayton Delaney Died -- Lady in the Harbor -- May I Borrow Some Sugar From You -- Last Cowboy Song -- Heroes -- The Teddy Bear Song -- Write Your Own Songs -- The Old Mother's Locket Trick.
      Also performed by Willie Nelson.
    - Wave (Box 33, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: SP 9-3002
    - Tide (Box 34, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: SP-9-3031
    - Wave (Box 34, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: SP-9-3002
    - Wave (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 9 3002
      Wave -- The Red Blouse -- Look to the Sky -- Batidinha -- Triste -- Mojave -- Dialogo -- Lamento -- Antigua -- Captain Bacardi.
    - The Stranger (Box 170, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: 1977
      Movin' Out (Anthony's Song) -- The Stranger -- Just the Way You Are -- Scenes From An Italian Restaurant -- Vienna -- Only the Good Die Young -- She's Always A Woman -- Get It Right the First Time -- Everybody Has A Dream.
    - Glass Houses, 1980 (Box 170, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: FC 36384
      You May Be Right -- Sometimes A Fantasy -- Don't Ask Me -- It's Still Rock And Roll To Me -- All For Leyna -- I Don't Want to Be Alone -- Sleeping With the Television On -- C'Etait Toi (You Were the One) -- Close to the Borderline -- Through the Long Night.
    - Baby Let's Kiss, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: SP 12225
    - Caribou, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: MCA-2116
      The Bitch Is Back -- Pinky -- Grimsby -- Dixie Lily -- Solar Prestige A Gammon -- You're So Static -- I've Seen The Saucers -- Stinker -- Don't Let the Sun Go Down On Me -- Ticking.
    - Madman Acros the Water, 1972 (Box 169, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: MCA-3003
      Tiny Dancer -- Levon -- Razor Face -- Madman Across the Water -- Indian Sunset -- Holiday Inn -- Rotten Peaches -- All the Nasties -- Goodbye.
    - Jesse Johnson's Revue, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 28)
      Publisher no.: SP 6-5024
      Be Your Man -- I Want My Girl -- She Won't Let Go -- Just TOo Much -- Let's Have Some Fun -- Can You Help Me -- Special Love -- She's A Doll.
    - Get Wise (Box 32, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: 75021 2381 1
    - Quincy Jones Live At Budokan (Box 32, Folder 34)
      Publisher no.: AMP -28045
    - The Best, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: SP 3200
    - Match Game, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: SP-5138
    - Walking In Space, 1969 (Box 171, Folder 36)
      Publisher no.: SP 9-3023
      Dead End -- Walking In Space -- Killer Joe -- Love and Peace -- I Never Told You -- Oh Happy Day.
    - The Dude, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 3721
      Ai No Corrida -- The Dude -- Just Once -- Betcha' Wouldn't Hurt Me -- Somethin' Special -- Razzamatazz -- One Hundred Ways -- Velas -- Turn on the Action.
    - Flying Home (Box 42, Folder 39)
      Publisher no.: E1-48682
    - Greatest Hits (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Closer to The Flame (Box 44, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: ST-53017
    - Girl Noise, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: 75021 7399 1
    - The Right To Rock, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Wanna Play Your Game, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      Publisher no.: SP 5073
    - Address of Senator Edward M. Kennedy, Democratic National Convention, August 12, 1980, 1980 August 12 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Songwriter (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Masabumi Kikuchi and Gil Evans (Box 45, Folder 26)
      Publisher no.: FX 8525
    - Love Me Tender (Box 44, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: MCA-5307
    - Gorgeous Love, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: 75021 7228 1
    - Blow My Fuse, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: 7 81877-1
    - I love you/ Let's ask the night (Box 41, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: BLX 105
    - [Selections], 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 43, Folder 15)
      Waters Part -- Blue Line.
      Selections from the I.R.S. album, "Cypress" (SP 70648).
    - Celebrate Me Home, 1977 (Box 170, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: 34423
      Celebrate Me Home -- Lady Luck -- I Believe In Love -- Why Do People Lie -- Daddy's Back -- Set It Free -- If You Be Wise -- Enter My Dream -- I've Got the Melody (Deep In My Heart) -- You Don't Know Me.
    - In High Adventure, 1982 (Box 170, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: TC 38127
      Don't Fight It -- Heartlight -- I Gotta Try -- Swear Your Love -- The More We Try -- Heart To Heart -- If It's Not What You're Looking For -- It Must Be Imagination -- Only A Miracle.
    - unspecified (Box 170, Folder 26)
    - Vox Humana, 1985 (Box 170, Folder 26)
      Publisher no.: FC 39174
      Vox Humana -- No Lookin' Back -- Let There Be Love -- I'll Be There -- I'm Gonna Do It Right -- Forever -- At Last -- Loraine -- Love Will Follow.
    - Sweet On U, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Johnny Maestro Sings His Biggest Hits With The Crests and The Brooklyn Bridge, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: H 1000
      Also performed by The Crests and The Brooklyn Bridge.
    - Ay Amor, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: S 84993
    - Children Of Sanchez, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: SP 6700
      Children Of Sanchez Overture -- Lullabye -- Fanfare -- Pilgrimage (Part I) -- Pilgrimage (Part II) -- Consuelo's Love Theme -- Hot Consuelo -- Death Scene -- Market Place -- Echano -- Bellavia -- Lullabye -- Medley -- B'Bye -- Children Of Sanchez Finale.
    - Wynton Marsalis, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: FC 37574
    - The Best Of Lena Martell, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: NSPL 18506
    - [Selections] (Box 62, Folder 4)
      On a clear day -- The shadow of your smile -- Just in time -- Somewhere -- Let There Be Love -- Call Me Irresponsible -- Girl From Ipenima -- Come Rain, Or Come Shine -- Rainy Day -- So Easy To Love -- All My Tomorrows.
    - Hugh Masekela's Latest (Box 169, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: 73010
      Baby, Baby, Baby -- Society's Child (Baby I've Been Thinking) -- Lily the Fox -- Groove Me -- Thula -- Mago -- Arrastao -- Reza (Laia Ladaia) -- I Just Wasn't Meant for These Times -- Here, There and Everywhere -- Mazeze.
    - Johnny Mathis Sings the Music of Bacharach & Kaempfert (Box 170, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: G 30350
      The Look of Love -- I'll Never Fall In Love Again -- Strangers In the Night -- Danke Schoen -- Walk On By -- Wonderland By Night -- The Times Will Change -- Don't Stay -- The Lady Smiles -- Remember When -- If There's A Way -- L-O-V-E -- Faithfully -- Heavenly -- Lady -- I Say A Little Prayer -- This Guy's In Love With You -- Odds And Ends -- Don't Go Breakin' My Heart -- Alfie -- Spanish Eyes.
    - Love Story (Box 170, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: C 30499